[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "How important is it to the family that you've managed to have this legal success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "It is incredible for the family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "I mean, what is the argument that stops somebody like Sarah from having this kind of transplant from an adult donor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Yes, it was a very puzzling argument, which was they didn't have enough data.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What is your view as a family of the secretary's position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "We don't understand it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "How hopeful are you, from all the experts have told you, that you may get one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "We're very hopeful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "If that was the circumstance, would you be in favor of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "My first question, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I'm doing well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Where were you when that happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "I had just been released from the hospital.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", ":", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "What were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "So we got to ride out and -- just not again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Now, Ashlynn, did you realize how serious the tornado was at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ashlynn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "And did you realize, Ashlynn, that your mom had been a hero in protecting all of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "After -- I was -- I was kind of the one who noticed that it was through her leg.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ashlynn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "And, Miranda, Miranda, what did you think when you saw your poor mother had this terrible spike in her leg?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, I didn't see it in her leg.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Miranda", "Miranda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Pretty scary to look at, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "How is the community generally coping with it all, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I think, as Oklahomans, we cope together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Security Agency"], "LOCATION": ["Boston"]}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, look, I think if what you're trying to do is avoid the kind of terrorism that occurred in Boston or the kind of terrorism that almost occurred in Times Square a couple years ago, I'm for whatever it takes as long as it's restricted to the National Security Agency and doesn't get involved in looking for criminal behavior or other kind of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2006"]}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "So, isn't it like for like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Let me go back to 2006.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Powell"]}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Why would you trust them anymore than you would trust the Obama administration with the same records?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Let me say, first of all, I don't believe Colin Powell lied.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["United States"], "TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What is your reaction to this news?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "The president of the United States has decided that he wants as his national security adviser a person who went on five shows in one Sunday morning and miss -- you go back to lies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 310, "question": "In a wonderful display of bipartisanship, would you have had exactly the same view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "No --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Piers, the difference is you're totally confusing the situations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Clinton"]}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, the first -- I said part of the difference is, there is no question that the Obama administration and Secretary Clinton's staff systematically lied to the American people knowingly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "But there is no evidence she did, though, is there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "That's why I said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Do you have any reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "I find that a disappointing appointment on the part of the president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Well, this is going to be a bad show because I agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Did she do a good job or not a good job?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I actually didn't watch it closely enough to have a clue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Are these the kind of things from your experience that can trigger in a young teenage girl like Paris with the background of her father's death and so on this kind of dramatic cry for help, if that's what it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Shaun, I mean, how much do you think goes back to the fact that she lost her father who she was incredibly close to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Do you know yet if it's a world record?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "We did not know it was a world record.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Yes, what I meant was, do you know yet, now that you have had it examined and weighed and stuff, do you know if you've broken the report?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "It's a pending world record right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "But wasn't it terrifying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yes, it -- it is terrifying, but any time you're that close to an apex predator or a food source, you really feel like you're just floating out there, and it's a very big shark teeth, they move around like lightning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "What is the technique for actually getting one of these things out of the water and on to a boat and taking it home with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]